<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SDS 348 Portfolio</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on SDS 348 Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Get To Know Me!</title>
      <link>/about/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/about/</guid>
      <description>Hey y’all! My name’s Kevin and I’m a junior biology student at the University of Texas at Austin.  I’m currently pursuing a B.S.A. in Biology with a minor in studio art.  I am going to be applying to optometry school soon – so wish me luck! My career goal is to open up my own private practice eye clinic one day. I think eyes are super neat, and I am determined to work hard in order to better serve my community in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OREO &amp; Python</title>
      <link>/blog/oreo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/oreo/</guid>
      <description>I found a really funny image on the internet related to oreos. Lets try to emulate this using Python and R!!   So basically: RE = Cream  O = Cookie  O + RE + O = an Oreo sandwich cookie   R Code Chunk library(reticulate) OREO &amp;lt;- &amp;quot;OREO&amp;quot;  Python Code Chunk I want 4 oreos! cookie = r.OREO print(cookie, cookie, cookie, cookie) ## (&amp;#39;OREO&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;OREO&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;OREO&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;OREO&amp;#39;)  Let’s separate the top cookie off the rest of the oreo #Python Code Chunk cookie[0] + &amp;#39;&amp;amp;&amp;#39; + &amp;#39; &amp;#39; + cookie[1:] ## &amp;#39;O&amp;amp; REO&amp;#39;  I hate the cream!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>/about/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/resume/</guid>
      <description>RESUME Contact Info Email: le.kevin03@gmail.com
github.com/kevtle
 Education  Associates of Science at Richland College (2015-2017) Bachelors of Science and Arts at the University of Texas at Austin w/ Studio Art Minor (2017-Present)   Skills  Experienced in Photoshop, Illustrator, Lightroom, Procreate (for iPad), Canva, and Microsoft Office Loves to be creative whenever applicable! Moderately experienced with R Studio and Python :)   Experience  40 hours shadowing experience at Constant Eye Care with Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Modeling, Testing, and Predicting</title>
      <link>/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project2/</guid>
      <description>(5 pts) Introduce your dataset and each of your variables (or just your main variables if you have lots) in a paragraph. What are they measuring? How many observations?  #My Data library(boot) view(aids) aids &amp;lt;- aids aids2&amp;lt;-aids The data that I chose for this project is a dataset called “aids” which deals with the delays in AIDS reporting in England and Wales. The dataset contains records about the reported cases of AIDS diagnosed from July 1983 to the end of 1992.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1: Exploratory Data Analysis with Tidyverse Tools</title>
      <link>/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project1/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown My Chosen Datasets cntygrad &amp;lt;- read.csv(&amp;quot;ResultsGrid_ExportData-2.csv&amp;quot;) cntyethnic &amp;lt;- read.csv(&amp;quot;ResultsGrid_ExportData.csv&amp;quot;) For this project, I decided to take a dataset on graduations and educations levels in all the counties across Texas and combine it with a dataset on the ethnic makeup of all the counties across Texas. The County Education dataset (labelled cntygrad) has the percentage of all the people in each county that graduated high school, completed their bachelors degree, or are unemployed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>Here are some projects I have recently completed:
  Exploratory Data Analysis with Tidyverse Tools
  Modeling, Testing, and Classification
  These projects were a blast to do, and I had a bunch of fun analyzing the data :)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>